Whoa!
Yuzawaya
So this is where you go to get fabric!
Thanks for coming with me today!
Please, I'm club president.
I'm happy to help.
I'm not sure what I want to do for my next costume.
I'm hoping to get inspired by some of
the fabrics and materials we see here today!
That's a cool way of figuring things out.
C'mon, let's go!
Can We Be Friends?
I've never been to this kind of store before.
Whoa, they have a whole cosplay section!
Of course!
Lots of their customers are cosplayers.
Made with cosplay materials!
People make those from scratch, too?!
Props are a must-have for fighter
characters or battleship girls!
I'll restock on my Liliel cosplay basics.
You can go hang out somewhere if you want.
Let me know if you want me to carry anything.
I'll need this, and this...
These have gotta be heavy...
Yeah, that's more what I was expecting.
You okay?
I can hold it for you if you want.
Sorry!
M-maybe I shouldn't have just grabbed
it out of her hands... Sorry!
Off-white stretch fabric and pink PVC...
Liliel?!
What? Wait, uh...
Ohmigosh, did she figure it out from the fabric alone?!
Fifth...
Huh?!
Wait, are you No-
RRRRUMBLE
Don't kill me!
Please don't be a knife!
Huh?
Cinderella Stars Cosplay Event?
Are you going to this event?
You want me to go?!
O-okay!
Ririsa?
W-what's that you have there?
Look.
Wait, Nonoa, as in the fourth place on that ranking?!
I think so.
And she invited you to this event?
I think she wants me to come see her.
But it didn't feel friendly...
She mentioned the ranking, right?
No way.
It was a challenge?!
So she wants you to compete
with her at this event, then?
I-I don't think she likes me...
Don't jump to conclusions!
You don't know if that's true!
I don't know why she'd be going after you, though.
She was ranked higher, right?
Maybe she wants to take me
out before I get too powerful?
Yeah, we can't really know what she's thinking...
Are you gonna take her up on it, Ririsa?
I want to believe all cosplayers
are friends and allies.
So I have to go!
I'm sure she's a good person, deep down!
I get that. Sounds good.
But how are you gonna cosplay at the event?
Liliel isn't in Cinderella Stars.
Senpai, how forgetful you are...
What?
Do you remember why you have Cinderella Stars
installed when you don't even play it?!
Oh! You're right!
I know what my next cosplay is now.
Wait, can you even finish in time?
The event is next week!
Who the hell do you think I am?
Okay, uh, who?
T-the avatar of Liliel?
You coulda just told me it was a rhetorical question.
Don't worry, I'm gonna get it done!
O-okay, then.
See, I'm okay. I'm not weird.
I'll wear Coulia again to the event.
Liliel...
If I could get her...
If I could get her to be my friend...
Here's what happened today...
When someone helped me,
I wanted to thank him,
but instead just glared at him.
Why am I like this?
So depressing? So antisocial?
I started cosplaying to make friends,
but I was too nervous to say anything,
let alone connect with any other cosplayers!
I'm scared to smile,
but I probably made everyone think I'm stuck up!
But I took a big leap forward today...
I can't believe I ran into Liliel!
She caught me off-guard,
but giving her that flyer turned
out to be the perfect move!
And she took it from me!
My invitation! My love letter!
I might actually make my first-ever friend!
Today's event isn't centered around cosplay, huh?
Yeah, it's for the first
anniversary of the game,
but they have a cosplay area set up.
Thanks for spending your Sunday with us, Sensei.
Yeah, especially when you suddenly give
me a week's notice to go to an event.
Being an advisor sure is hard work!
Is that a new camera?!
Did you seriously buy a camera that's
better than the one we have in our club?!
Behold, the power of a public servant's credit limit!
...Liliel-chan!
She's actually here!
H-how do I play this?!
Say something. Say hi!
C'mon, let's do this!
Three, two, o-o-o-one...
Oh?
Oh! Good morning.
RRRRUMBLE
Oh no, I'm freaking her out!
She thinks I'm some weirdo!
I have to say something,
or she won't like me!
But I'm too scared I'll say something stupid!
Hey, Nonoa-chan, uh...
If I'm going to screw things up anyways,
maybe I shouldn't say anything at all.
Why did I run away?!
I'm being weird again! I'm so stupid!
I guess she doesn't like me after all...
Hey, Liliel!
Liliel-chan just started,
but she already has friends?
She's so cool...
Nagomi-san! What cosplay is that?
It's not cosplay.
Hey there, Nagomi-san.
H-hi, K-Kai-sama!
The name's Okumura.
You've still got terrible fashion sense, huh?
Excuse me?!
This outfit is cute- wait, Mayura?!
Nagomi-san and Mayura-san?!
They're Heavenly Queens!
Even I've heard of them!
So how do you guys know each other?
Well, she's my Sensei at-
I'm keeping this a secret at school,
so keep the school stuff a secret out here!
R-right, sorry.
She's your Sensei?
Yeah, that's right!
She's my apprentice!
Is that right?
No wonder I thought of Mayura
the second I saw her.
I get it!
That must mean you're endorsing
Liliel to take your throne when you retire!
Great. Now she's going to spread
that rumor like wildfire.
Are you cosplaying here, too?
I can't wait to see it!
You know it! I'm an official guest!
I'm booked at basically all the events in town.
You are?!
I bet you're thinking how
annoying that's gonna be!
Fine, then, I won't bother saying hi!
So...
So I'll get to see you at every single cosplay event?
That's awesome!
How is she so goddamn adorable?! Ugh!
I get to see her more often than you!
Why're you bragging about that?!
WOBBLE
I can't win. Her friends are too cool.
We won't get along.
She'll never be my friend.
It's pretty surprising how
many people are here, huh?
Huh?! Yeah!
Kai-sama is talking to me!
For an event that's not cosplay-centric,
COSPLAYER CHECK-IN
there sure are a lot of
cosplayers and photographers.
Maybe it's because I'm here as a guest!
That's gotta be it!
I was just kidding, geez!
Everyone's gotta be here for her.
See them all?
All the Coulia fans?
Everyone's talking about the Five Rising Stars.
Well, the first two they posted.
They're talking about me.
Wait, did she invite you to this event?
Do you know her?
Uh, kinda?
She challenged me to a duel, I think.
A duel?!
Another cosplayer picked a fight with you?!
I know I'm the last one to talk, but still.
So you were picking a fight with her.
I mean...
there are tons of cosplayers out there
who see everyone as a rival to compete with.
You mean, like you?
But that friendly rivalry's part of the fun, isn't it?
I won't deny that.
Especially since you enjoyed it.
What's that look for?!
I remember my newbie days now! Come on!
She's still the same.
I'm not saying anything.
I wish we could be friends...
O-oh, no, they totally have the wrong idea!
I made the worst first impression ever!
There's no way we can be friends now...
I-I should just give up, but...
Noa-chan, this is awesome!
You drew Liliel!
You're so good! Draw me next!
When I was little,
I could make friends just by doing what I liked.
I wasn't weird.
Little kids are all otaku.
But, while all the normal kids figured that out,
I completely missed it.
Noa-chan's drawing stuff again.
Does she ever study for tests?
You're quitting the baseball team?
I gotta study.
And while everyone grew out of it,
I stayed an otaku.
I was all by myself.
Noa, why aren't you studying?!
Stop wasting your time!
Get rid of that!
You're not a little kid anymore!
I'm weird.
But...
What should we do for the next one?
Let's do a ParaDol group!
I'll be Suffy-chan!
I hope I've got some PTO.
That's so cool.
So there are adults who have friends
they can enjoy their hobbies with.
Come on. I can't give up now!
I don't want to give up the things I like!
I want to be proud of them!
And I want friends who feel the same way!
I'll give it one more try.
If I put all my effort into the things I love,
maybe I can make a friend!
I cosplayed for the first time.
The girl in the mirror felt like another person.
I didn't feel weird at all.
I felt like I could do anything.
I could even make friends.
But my first event was a total bust.
Maybe I'm not cut out for this.
A Liliel? Nowadays?
She's probably loved her favorite
series for a really long time.
She's so cool.
I bet just talking to her would make me so happy.
If I could get her to be my friend,
I'd be so happy...
I-I can't give up!
Today's the day!
I'm going to make a change!
I'm going to make my first friend ever!
It's the moment you've been waiting for,
Cinderella Star fans!
Introducing our special guest, Nagomi-san!
Nagomi-san is headed to the photo area now,
so we hope you'll see her there!
See you soon!
I'm gonna crush all of you.
Liliel, we're not competing today.
We don't need to try
and outshine each other at all.
RUUUMBLE
But I won't complain if I come out on top!
Nagomi-san is really fired up today, huh...
She's regained her confidence.
That posture says she thinks
she's the cutest one here.
This might be her most powerful form yet.
I hope Ririsa's okay.
Changing Room
Yeah, she's taking a while to change.
Should we check on her?
It's packed in here! Look at all the idols!
I gotta clear things up with her...
That spot's open.
GLARE
Go ahead! I'll go change in that corner!
Wait, no!
I screwed up again. That's three in a row.
It's fine.
I'll try again after I get changed.
I'm sure I'll feel different once I'm in costume.
Wait, what's Liliel-chan going to wear?!
I didn't even think of that when
I invited her out to this event!
I'm so stupid!
I thought she was so cool for cosplaying Liliel,
and now I'm making her do something else!
Did she really put together a
Cinderella Stars cosplay in a whole week?
Because I told her to?
I'm the worst. My heart hurts.
So I've seen her cosplay,
but who is she?
I don't know anything about this game.
Wait, you've already seen her costume?
She came crying to me yesterday,
Sensei!
so I helped her finish her costume.
I've got you.
That's how she got it done in a week!
You're too nice!
Sure, but her costume looks clean as hell.
Asking a Heavenly Queen is cheating!
I never thought she'd do
someone who wasn't Liliel.
I almost want to ask if she's okay.
Oh, she's more than okay.
Thanks for waiting!
W-what do you think?
She's so cute!
Wait, you're Liliel!
C'mon, Sensei.
Angel Liliel On Stage!
Of course Shonen Jump has a
collab with Cinderella Stars!
Your girl's in everything, geez!
Humanity is in danger,
and only one angel can teach
them how to work together:
when she's reborn in the modern age and
starts a singing career in this idol AU!
Hell yeah!
The app developers totally
understood the source material!
I don't have money to pay
for premium gacha odds,
but I played all through class and got her!
I love that you're dedicated,
but save some dedication for school, okay?
This skirt's a lot shorter than usual, though.
You sure about this one?
I've got bloomers on, see?
I didn't need to see them!
Liliel-chan is so freaking cute!
It's so cool that Liliel's in Cinderella Stars, too!
Oh, please, please let this happen!
We could take pictures together,
side-by-side!
And then we could talk about doing
a group cosplay from her anime next...
And I'll do whatever goes best with Liliel!
Angel, demon, whatever she wants!
Then we'll go out in cosplay together
and everyone will love us...
Whoa, it's that Liliel cosplayer!
Coulia's here, too!
Nonoa-chan!
Did you read Mr. Camera's post?
Of course I did!
I can't believe two of his
Rising Stars are here to battle!
Thank you!
I didn't want this to be a battle...
Everyone's looking at us.
It wouldn't be weird for me
to say something to her!
Just summon up your courage and say,
"Hello, want to take pictures together?"
Whoa!
W-want to...
O-oh, damn...
It's a face-off! A cosplay face-off, man!
No, it's not!
Cosplayers don't do face-offs!
I want to take pictures together!
I-it's hopeless.
Even if I tried, they'd just get the
wrong idea about Liliel-chan, too.
I should go-
Hey!
Would you like to take pictures with me?
Wait, did she just ask if
I want to take pictures with her?
No way, she'd never ask someone like me to do that.
I must have imagined it.
She straight-up ignored Liliel-chan!
That's cold!
No! I wasted my one and only chance!
And I made Liliel-chan look like an idiot!
I have to turn around...
It's getting crowded.
Let's find a spot and get things started!
O-okay!
Why?! Why am I like this?!
I tried to say something,
but it felt like the words were caught in my throat...
We'd all be better off if you...
Hey, Nonoa-chan, could I get a picture?
Wait, what?!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You've got it all wrong.
I didn't come here to get my picture taken.
I came here to be friends with Liliel-chan.
Now there's no point in me being here.
It's weird. I used to be able to talk.
ANIME CLUB
So my headcanon is that Himari-chan was
worried about the age gap between her and Raia,
and that's why she didn't-
Sheesh, Noa-chan, you like,
only talk about stuff you care about.
Uh, yeah. I could go on forever about manga.
Weirdo.
Like, you just keep rambling,
and don't even try to connect it with our conversation.
It's like you don't even listen to us.
Conversation's supposed to go back-and-forth!
I know, right?
I bet instead of listening,
you're just planning out what you wanna say next.
That's not communication, you know.
We'd all be better off if you didn't talk.
That's right.
People hate it when I talk.
I'm weird when I talk.
I'm the same as I was back then.
I haven't changed at all.
Cosplay didn't make a difference.
Hey!
Together with You